Meet Dory 0.3.2.
Your complete local Linux workspace,
built for Apple Silicon Macs.
Start with one smaller Docker Core.
About 112 MB of duplicate compatibility payload—gone.
Then add only what you need: Kubernetes, Linux Machines,
Debian, Ubuntu, or Kali desktops.
Run and test graphical Linux applications beside your containers:
Retina-sharp windows, persistent disks, scoped Mac folders, and snapshots.
For AI agents, launch a dedicated Preview sandbox VM.
No host files are visible by default.
Mount only what you choose.
Set network to none.
Roll back.
Or let the temporary VM delete itself.
Optional components are signed and removable.
Your workload data stays.
Add custom domains. Add trusted HTTPS.
Dory. Smaller core. Bigger possibilities.
Built for Mac. Open source.